Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ anhnguyen2024 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

End-user manuals
Functional Testing
Software Documentation

Honors-Awards

Excellent staff

Anh Nguyen Canh

IT Business Analyst and Project Manager at FIS Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Seasoned Business Analyst with 3+ years of experience, especially in the banking sector. I have also taken on the role of project manager and coordinator for many foreign subcontractor projects. I excel at gathering and clarifying stakeholders needs & requirements and proposing solutions. Always seeking to expand my knowledge, currently learning about AI techniques to automate repetitive tasks and improve my workflow efficiency.

Experience

FPT Information System
Business Analyst
September 2021 - Present (3 years 7 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Cadena HRM
Consultant
August 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 2 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

University of Finance & Marketing - UFM

Bachelor of management information system · (September 2013 - January 2018)